AMRIZ JANTAN

Junior Full-Stack Developer

SUMMARY

Certified Full Stack Developer with analytical and creative skills in addition to strong entrepreneurship.

Multidisciplinary background with 7+ years experience in business development that includes both physical and digital operations as Co-founder of a Japanese lifestyle store and fashion label. Highly skilled in complex risk assessment and key corporate client advisory with 9+ years experience in the corporate environment as a Senior Risk Analyst.

CONTACT

Phone: +49 (0)176 3228 2463

Email: amrizjantan@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/amrizjantan

Linkedin: amriz jantan

Portfolio: amrizjantan.github.io/

Portfolio-Revamp/

Address: 20357 Hamburg, Germany.

Open to remote roles.

SKILLS

HTML / CSS

Javascript

MERN stack

MEAN stack

REST api

Angular

React

MongoDB

NODE.js

AWS

Wordpress

LANGUAGES

English – Advanced German – Advanced Bahasa Malaysia – Native Japanese - Basic

WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2021 to present

Junior Full-Stack Developer, Freelance

Hamburg and Berlin, Germany

- Designed, developed and maintained an on-line shop www.bluesleeve.de with Wordpress technology that successfully digitalized the business operation, increased sales and customer awareness.
- Accordingly worked on 6 projects with various latest technologies and acquired new skills that eventually lead to a completion of a 6-month coding program.

October 2014 to present

Co-Founder, Bluesleeve Japanese lifestyle Store

Hamburg, Germany

- Assumed full responsibility in creating business modules, plans and goals that ensured maximum profits and return on investment.
- Oversaw all aspects of business development, daily retail and on-line activities which maintained effective and smooth business operations.
- Collaborated and coordinated with artists, designers and partners on art exhibitions and business projects that increased shop's reputation and products diversity.
- Ensured timely preparation of business accounting and tax submission resulted to stable cash flow management and regulator's compliant.
- Offered professional advise and shopping experience in order to maintain customer satisfaction and retention.

January 2008 to October 2013

Risk Analyst, AON Corporation

Hamburg, Germany

- Analysed client's complex risk portfolio to identify and measure political, management, financial and non-financial exposures to possible loss prior to designing a comprehensive Risk Management.
- Advised key corporate clients on risk policies and processes in accordance to the designed framework that ensured successful risk mitigation and business contingency.

EDUCATION

2022

Full-Stack Web Development Program

Career Foundry Berlin, Germany

2002

Bachelors Degree, Risk Management

MARA University of Technology Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia